and we're back to these um so we talk
about two
realities and there's the there's the
real reality Ultimate Reality and then
there's fake reality and there's a huge
argument about fake reality so Ultimate
Reality obviously if you can see it
directly once if you can touch the
diamond
world uh it changes you
forever
usually the karma of a thing
is decided by your motivation
usually uh if you have a good motivation
and you try to help somebody for example
even if you
fail the motivation is the main Good
Karma okay so if you try to help people
even if you fail to help them you
succeeded because the motivation is
everything okay in one case
especially uh it's not the motivation
it's the object okay the karma comes
from the object and that's emptiness
okay anything you do about
Emptiness is a powerful Karma even if
you have a lousy motivation okay it's
very interesting okay because the object
is so holy the object is so powerful
even a idiot who tries to do something
with emptiness will have a great result
you see what I mean
uh and it's not so much depending on the
on the
motivation uh I mean of course if you
have a good motivation to see emptiness
that's better but if you see emptiness
it almost doesn't matter what's your
motivation it's the highest Karma you
can make because of the object because
the object is so holy you see what I
mean
uh that's Ultimate Reality if you can
see it for 20 minutes in your life
uh that's the most important thing you
can do in your life okay then that then
you spent your life well it's kind of a
good deal you can waste your whole
life watching
Netflix having
fun and if you just see emptiness for 20
minutes uh it was a good
strategy okay uh it's the 20 minutes
okay in this lifetime the most important
thing you can do is to see iness
directly okay but you can't do it all
day it's extremely expensive Karma to
see emptiness it's very expensive Karma
to sit in a class where they talk about
emptiness okay and you know people
worried about how well are you taking
care of your
kids you're extremely good person
already if you're here okay okay if
you're here you can tell everybody they
say you're kind of stupid you say yeah
but I was in the
class or you're not taking very good kid
of your kids care of your kids yeah but
I was in the
class uh if you make it to this class uh
you are one in a million literally you
are one in a million so try to think
about it some sometimes when you feel
down about
yourself and you feel like you have 10
things to confess and no things to
Rejoice that happens to me like the
confession goes on and on and on and
then I'm like let's do rejoicing I'm
like I can't think of
anything uh you're here okay if you're
here you must have some extraordinary
Karma you are one in a million and I I
mean literally you are one in a million
okay for every person who's here there's
99999999999 who are not here you are
special to be a bad person in this room
is better than being a good person
somewhere
else
[Applause]
okay okay so uh that's just the EMP
power of emptiness and it doesn't so
much depend on you okay it's a good it's
a good deal okay then there's fake
reality okay fake reality so no matter
how amazing you
are it's very unusual to spend 20
minutes in Ultimate Reality ever okay
very very unusual in your whole life
okay then the rest of the the
lifetime the rest of the 69 years or
whatever 11 months and 29 days and 23 in
hours and 40
minutes uh you know you live in fake
reality you live in this fake reality
okay and there's two kinds of fake
reality
okay uh one is called real fake reality
and one is fake fake reality okay and I
wanted to talk about that okay
uh and we're and it's specifically with
Dharma okay uh the Dharma is there's
real Dharma and then there's fake Dharma
but the fake Dharma
works okay there's real Dharma and then
there's fake Dharma and the fake Dharma
works and if you don't believe
so then please
watch the extraordinary attorney woo
Korean soap opera I'm into Korean soap
operas now I don't
know
uh even though you know it's fake you
start crying you know like you know the
the actress she she finishes filming and
she goes and drinks in the bar or
something but uh during the yeah I don't
you can't help but cry uh or you know
they when they finally kiss after 12
episodes only Koreans can have almost
kiss for 12 11
episodes and then uh somebody there's a
car
acent
and but uh it's all fake but it's very
moving and it changes your behavior for
the day you know it's fake it's a fake
TV show but it makes you feel more
compassionate and more romantic uh the
whole day or half a day that's why you
have to watch it twice a day uh
so you know uh something fake can still
influence us and that's the point okay
then there's a huge
argument in
Buddhism is there a fake fake reality
and is there a real fake reality and
they say yes okay they say yes so I
wanted to talk about that uh I'm working
on it in somebody's books sometimes
together I can't remember whose book it
was
uh but uh here's an example here by the
way it's called Uh K
Sayo
d dund means Ultimate Reality uh it's
emptiness okay especially when you see
it directly dund Ultimate Reality you
can only do that 20 minutes in 10
years so uh then the rest of the time
you are
in
say which means fake reality
okay it's not fake because it's not real
it's fake because it fools you it's
deceptive okay it's not what it looks
like it looks like it's not coming from
you but it is coming from you so we call
it fi okay it's coming from you that's
real but you don't understand it's
coming from you even if you sat in this
room for year after year you you go to
the kitchen and they serve you breakfast
and you say I the toast is too
hard and and you look at the cook and
you're like you know actually you should
go on the toilet and look in the mirror
and say the toast is too hard you know
like that
okay all bad opinions should be in the
toilet okay all meditation also uh okay
so anyway that's a fake reality and and
you live in that reality
okay then there's times
uh you're eating the toast which you is
too cook too hard for you and you want
to blame the cook and you bite the toast
and you're
like and that means you got the
gluten-free
toast that was that was made for
Ellie and uh she probably got your
gluten full toast and uh okay so
sometimes there's a fake fake Mei got it
you thought it was real toast and it
turned out to be gluten-free toast and
you know see see what I mean so that's
fake fake reality now I'll give $100
well everybody woke
up the best cure for postpartum is
$100 okay you ready
why did I put these two books up
here first of all you have to raise your
hand secondly the Box lady has to choose
you thirdly you have to say it
loud okay why did I why did I use these
two pages to talk about fake fake
reality they are different pages of the
same book nice so one is fake and the
other is ult one yeah no one is real
fake reality and one is fake fake
reality got it okay do you want to know
which one is wish
uh the bottom one is the real fake
reality and the top one let me make
sure Chloe s uh yeah it is I
checked it says here it says oali it
says oali the bottom it says in fact it
has a picture of upani on the left side
okay the one who started the Via holding
custom
okay the point is you can still learn
from both books okay you will still
learn something from both books but one
is the real one and one is the
we don't know we we'll probably never
know the story I'm curious I don't think
we'll ever know but probably I'm
guessing the story I want to
spread is that uh he wrote the top one
20 years
earlier and then he study study study
study and then he wrote the he updated
his book right
again uh
later and he improved it it's improved a
lot uh but they are both fake why $100
question they are both fake
why the discussion is who wrote it right
I'll give you a
clue I just gave you an obvious clue co
co hi there I think because neither of
them them are the direct perception of
emptiness no it's okay do you have K do
you have an idea
by the way I want to thank Vietnam one
more
[Applause]
time I tried to raise
$1,700 for a stupid little vacuum
cleaner and I couldn't do it I mean it
was difficult but you mentioned to the
Vietnamese that we need 300
$100,000 for a new volunteer cabin and
they're
like they they as a group they raise
half the money already thank
[Applause]
you but but can he answer the
question that's what was the
question
F yeah why is it fake
good I I'll by the way I'll give you a
clue okay it's $25
clue uh it looks like we're discussing
who wrote
it but but okay um my answer is because
um the real the real dharm is when you
you uh see the uh the the Dharma make
you see the emptiness direct directly
that's a real Dharma and all the book
all the Sha is a fake Dharma that's nice
and now the the fake Dharma itself right
now we're talking fake fake Dharma and
real fake
Dharma why is this fake fake Dharma who
wrote This
Book wait you say it cuz he get M the
book coming from my S you wrote the book
yeah
$100
[Applause]
it's fake fake because it doesn't look
like he wrote the book we're arguing
which one did he write first did he
really write both of them you know and
then the truth
is you wrote both of them okay so I'll
ask you why you wrote two different ones
okay all right okay got
it why is is it important to know about
fake
reality then you cannot blame other
people for your reality okay you cannot
blame other people for your reality okay
and if we're talking about coffee
meditation yeah you can you can
like somebody says the sweet rolls in
this Cafe are unbelievable and you're
like yeah oh I created those okay got
it all right uh here's the quotation
from Aaj that talks about the two
realities
okay yeah by the way a lot of these
teachings came from nagaj okay the
ultimate source is nagaj all right
so uh it's cool to know this book wisdom
okay if you study a long time and you
learn many different things slowly you
will realize they come from the gaj you
know that a lot of them come from the
gaj um by the way we we dedicated one of
the 12
translators just to ngago he's GNA spend
the rest of his life doing the G whether
he wants to or not uh and that's Nick
lha and
[Applause]
yeah and he finished a a very important
beautiful book called the 60 verses it's
called the 60 verses on proving
emptiness okay and uh we just finished
it it's 670 pages and it's it
was mental
Bloodshed like a lot of suffering to
finish that book but he finished it and
now he's on another book by ner called
ratnamala which is the string of jewels
okay and he's having his next class
tomorrow so if you're interested uh by
the way it goes very very deep tomorrow
I'm just if you want to have fun and
you're having
postpartum uh come to Nick's class
tomorrow it starts at 400
PM Arizona world
time okay some people say Paris is the
center of the world time some people say
England but it's Arizona some people say
beia okay all right uh here's nag when
the Buddhas teach the Dharma they use
both realities these are the deceptive
reality of the world and the reality
which is Ultimate okay so normal
people who never heard about anything to
do with
emptiness uh they are living in a real
world okay but it's fake okay they are
living in a real world but it's fake why
is it fake it doesn't look like it's
coming from them but it is coming from
them therefore it's artificial okay got
it
cool all right how does that what's that
have to do with a prayer that we can
help people in
prison we made the
prison okay we made the we oh I'm going
today to teach at the prison you know
and well who made the prison you made
the
prison I want to show I to show give me
one second okay see if I can find
this I have a sweet picture of this
place let's
see come on come
on
oh yeah I'm gonna Tim I'll send you some
pictures when you're ready you put them
up
okay should I send it to you
Tim Al Al
okay
[Music]
right
hang on hang
on
okay
okay tell me when it's ready you guys
okay all
right let's go to the next you guys
ready with the next
picture
um yeah uh this relates to the seventh
prayer of good name and the seventh
prayer of good name is that I pray that
all the conflict in the world will end
so it's a very nice prayer for us for
nowadays and um what
this picture is showing conflict in a
family okay and
uh it makes me think of two
conversations I've had in my life okay
so I grew up with uh I had two friends
in third grade I'm 9 years old and I had
two close friends and uh we're still
friends okay so 61 years later we are
still really really good friends and uh
one of the guys is Christian he's very
very Christian and
um and I was doing a retreat I was doing
a lay room retreat in in
flexa in a in a small cabin and uh he
wrote me and he said can I can I visit
you and I'm like well not normally we
don't do that but he said I don't know I
really want to talk to you about stuff
and and so I said okay come you know and
he came and we had long conversations
about
are are we're both into our own religion
and and we had long talks from the heart
because we we love each other very much
and uh and he listened very carefully to
all these ideas about Ultimate Reality
and decept he listened to it carefully
and then he said uh you know I love you
I respect your opinions but I have a
problem with your
ideas you know and I'm like I'm like G
you
know you know and he's he's like uh so
according to you
then uh the reality that I see in the
world is it's all coming from me there's
nothing that's not coming from me so
obviously if I meet irritating people at
diamond mountain and they do exist
here okay in fact we try to collect this
many together here as we can uh to help
the students
improve uh so don't be surprised if you
meet a really irritating person here
because we recruit them uh just for you
so uh anyway uh he said so I understand
this idea that you know not just
irritating people but all the people I
meet are
and the whole world is coming from from
me and he and I said yeah that's right
and he said well what's the goal what
what's the purpose to be a Buddhist you
what are you trying to do and I said if
it's coming from
you you can change it into a Buddha
Paradise you see what I mean if you are
more careful about the seeds that you
plant then you can create you can change
this world into a paradise yourself you
can be the one who changes this world
into Paradise if if the pen is
correct then you have power to change
this world into a paradise and he said I
wouldn't want
to I wouldn't want to and I'm like what
are you talking about you know isn't
that the goal of your you don't you want
to go to heaven or what are you talking
about you know you know and he
said if when I go to heaven it's going
to be different and I said well how and
he said I didn't make
it you know it's there and I did not
make it I'm going to heaven which I did
not make somebody else made it okay and
I said well if it's Heaven who cares you
know you know I'm like if it's Heaven I
don't care who made it who made this
beautiful car I'll take it
you know if it's the Toyota or Merc I
don't care and then he said he had a
he's not stupid and he and he has a big
big heart and he said if I create a
world where I where I experience
suffering as
Paradise then I won't be aware of the
other people who are in pain and that to
me is
unacceptable and I was like whoa you
know that's a
pretty beautiful idea I'll say it again
if the world's coming from
me and if the goal of understanding that
is to create a perfect world a mandala
right a beautiful
paradise then at that time when you
reach it you will only be aware of
beauty you know and then he said what
about all the other people that then
they're not they don't see Paradise even
in the same room they don't see Paradise
but if you see Paradise then what's
going to happen to them and he said I I
thought you guys had compassion I
thought you guys care about the other
people who are suffering how can you say
your goal is to live in a paradise where
no one is suffering and then what's
going to happen to everybody else who's
still suffering how how you going to
help them if you can't see them you know
what I mean if your Paradise is perfect
and everybody else is having a bad day
and you're having a good day in your
Paradise how can you be happy in your
Paradise if other people are not having
to Paradise you know and then I have the
same uh dis the same exact by the way
he's worried that we won't have
compassion uh that's his and I thought
it was a beautiful
thing to say because I never thought
about it and I'm like wow that's pretty
good and then uh we had a famous uh
debate that I remember I was in U I was
in the monastery I was in the gashi
course I was almost finished with my
gashi course and uh they have a they
have
a exam debate Examination for the new
GES right and it's very difficult my
class had
60 uh guess she 60 people started in my
class two people finished and it's very
difficult it's really really difficult
so at the
end you get examined for three weeks by
every monk in the monastery 2,000 people
3,000 people you get questioned by
everyone and it takes weeks and weeks
you know and I have a picture it's cute
uh I'm
like but
uh then in your college so there's 12
colleges in my Monastery each college
has about I don't know 50 monks 100
monks and those colleges are ancient
those colleges have been there for a
thousand years and um so in your
college uh the examination of the gishi
candidate the debate has to be started
by the oldest
nonesi okay the the one who starts the
questions for the gesi candidate has to
be the one who's coming up next like
next
year uh so the the
senior
anes has to ask the qu the first
questions to the gashi candidate so the
other cool thing is uh pon
who wrote the L Rim that we've been
studying for 13 14 years which is one of
the greatest books in history he's from
my
college okay which is your college
because you're my student so you belong
to my college by the way I don't care if
you don't want
to you're automatically uh say G on
College G yeah you are gon
College if you meet some Tibetan
somewhere in monk in the airport you say
I'm from
gon I forg on College it's like Arizona
college or something College okay yeah
RR
college so anyway uh so I I was the
Pabon is from my college he's our most
famous graduate a lar college and the
third one was taking his gashi
exam uh the second one finished his
gashi and died a week
later he was a refugee uh from the war
and uh and he died suddenly and then the
third
one uh it was my job to ask the question
I had to give the first question so I
gave that question you know I said uh
will there come a time when when I live
in a paradise so I'm debating him and
everyone's
like and it's a lot of pressure because
you got Ari M me what's AR M me the big
white
guy he's asking a question you know and
very strange looks like very strange
thing and uh and he's like will there
come a time when we reach Paradise
you know and he said yes and then I said
you know what's the paradise going to be
like and he said everything perfect you
know that everything would be perfect
then then I remembered my friend's
question my Christian friend's question
I remembered it and I said so you know
when you become a Buddha what's your
job what do you do and he said well you
teach you take care of people you know
and I said who do you take care of and
he said suffering people and I said but
you're living in a par there are no
suffering people where do you find
suffering people to teach when you
become a Buddha it seems like a silly
thing it's like you go to law school and
the day you graduate there's no more
Court you know right it's like why waste
the time you know uh if you become
Buddha everyone around you is a
beautiful person then who are you
helping and um it got very hot it got
very hot and then I got
holas olaso means uh there's a debate
master and he says
[Laughter]
enaas means next
debater and I'm like I'm not finished
you
know G is about to tell me the answer
I've been waiting for 20 years you know
and he's like oh he's like OHA go like
[Laughter]
this they they'll beat you in know you
think this is for
mess you know I'm like okay okay and uh
I have another teacher uh and he was my
logic teacher and and uh he said come
out on the porch let's keep going and it
was very cool so We snuck out on the
porch he's still getting his examination
and like 20 of us move out on the porch
and we kept going you know and this
teacher became the head of the tantry
college he's uh he's now the he is the
former head of the T College which means
he's next in line to be the for the
throne of SOA
uh which is the highest position in our
vage so uh so he's like he's also from
my college of course no wait he's no
he's not from my college anyway he said
come out and let's keep going you know
and we went for two three hours uh we
arguing this thing uh will you ever see
an end of conflict there's the picture
right will you ever see the end of
conflict the answer is yes
does that mean conflict ended in the
world can you reach the end of poverty
can you help all the
prisoners can you achieve the prayers of
medicine
Buddha and then what happens to
everybody
else there's this contradiction okay and
I want you to we call it in English we
say sit with it there's a contradiction
okay if you succeed in medicine Buddha
practice
right then there will be no prisoners in
the world because they'll all be Buddhas
okay but can there still be prisoners in
the
world can all those prisoners become
tantor
co-workers right and they they don't
exist in prison
anymore uh but can there can there still
be a people suffering in the world if if
the Buddha turned it into Paradise
already what do you
think and I think I mean where I'm at
okay here's yeah to him here's my
opinion okay here's after many years of
debating in and like here's my opinion
uh yeah I can reach a
place where all the people around me
appear as bogini I can I can reach a
place like
that but that doesn't mean that they see
it that way that way okay so there could
be a close friend of mine with cancer
and I see them as
vaj but they see themselves as a cancer
patient okay but Gula that means all the
suffering in the world wasn't finished
medicine Buddhist prayers were not
completed and I say no they were
completed the prayer work okay there's
no more prisoners in my
world okay but guess there's people who
still them see themselves in
prison no no contradiction it has to be
that way it will be that way it doesn't
mean I'm not in
Paradise or do we have to does everybody
have to be in Paradise before anybody
can be in
Paradise in in my world everybody will
be in Paradise you see what I mean G so
what you're saying is the all the
prisoners who look like prisoners now
might not be
prisoners I'll say it again if what
you're saying is correct then all the
prisoners who look like prisoners now
might not be
prisoners they might be
actors we have a tantric joke in the old
diamond mountain we there's a the movie
the movie
filming
company they have a department called
Central
Casting and that's where you go to that
department when you're making a movie
and you say I need a bad guy and they
say we got six bad guys you know and you
say I need one to like kill his mother
or something oh we got one of those and
then they they called Joe they come come
and he comes in and he's
like and it's all movie actors right
they're from Central Casting so there's
an a Joe in the old diamond mountain
that says uh why did Central Casting
send this guy you know there's a Central
casting in the Buddha
paradise and they say which Buddha look
most like a criminal you know and they
say oh you look you look like pretty
much like a criminal and then they yeah
the guy in this oh there he is yeah this
is one of our students by the way in the
prison he killed somebody he'll be in
the prison for the rest of his life he
cannot get out he will never get out he
will die in the prison and uh we taught
him
meditation and he's a very good
meditator and he's he's doing really
really well okay but maybe he's not a
prisoner maybe he's from Central Casting
maybe the the film of my life maybe they
called maybe they called him they said
we need a big tough guy who looks like
he's impossible that he's a Buddha and
then they said that's what barava is all
about right yanta that's that's what
these are all guys from Central
Casting okay so anyway you never know
who's who and that's a very very
healthy attitude for your life okay
maybe there's no Buddha in this room
maybe everybody except gesla is a Buddha
maybe they let G teach so he can learn
something thank you for that okay uh
okay
we don't know and the one thing we know
is we don't know so it's safer to assume
there might be at least a few Buddhas in
the room and they might look like s gang
or not okay we don't know okay uh by the
way I want to show a Buddha picture you
guys ready who's got that
cat so uh the friends from New Jersey uh
from the comic Mongolian Community who
are
here uh the moms are here the kids went
to have fun uh Maria Ludy and
S uh they presented a
painting uh it's got something on the
back can you read it cat you got your
eyeglasses on loud to gashi Michael
Roach and your
students thank you for your thoughtful
contributions toward our Temple upkeep
and
repairs we really appreciate all you
have done for us thank you the Rashi
ging
[Music]
Temple
[Applause]
uh so I think it's a big big blessing
this is the temple where my teachers
served for many years and uh we'll keep
it in our Temple here and we'll show it
here and thank you very
[Applause]
much and thank you for coming and we
hope you come many many times yes okay
and
uh we by the way I got a call from Rosa
she's in charge of the book press
Diamond cutor press and she goes gesla
you made a big mistake and I'm like what
is it this time and she said uh you did
a big advertisement for the taba BG for
the temple to raise money for the Rashi
ging temple in New Jersey and that book
is out of
print so I got all these orders what do
you want me to do you know there's no
books
oh wow well I said how about since we
are a book company why don't we publish
them so we are publishing more copies
and we promis to give uh all the money
to the temple okay and she's fighting
with
Amazon uh because they want a lot of the
profit and we're having a big amazon War
so anyway the Temple's going to get all
the income from the new book okay so
thank you
guys all right
uh so the the seventh prayer is no more
war no more fighting in the world okay
uh
and let's go to the next
one uh Tim how much time I got 15 15
minutes oh my God okay are you going to
do endless things after that
or does that included in my 15 or
not see I know
him
okay I'll stop in seven okay I'm at a
good place actually okay so when I
finish I'll call you up to to give
thanks to everybody all right uh 555
yeah 555 franisco
it's
uh
5.55 it's yeah
[Music]
good
um there's what do you
call there's a lot of verses in this
book and this is maybe the most famous
one okay so I thought it's a good place
to stop okay before we go and then we'll
continue next fall next October right uh
we'll finish this book and we'll finish
medicine Buddha by the great fifth D
okay uh but this is a really good place
to to finish to this this week
okay
uh everything is right with anything for
which Emptiness is right nothing is
right with anything for which Emptiness
is not right this is one of the most
famous teachings of Nag this is one of
the most famous emptiness teachings of
all time and it's a
reaction okay it's a reaction it's an
answer to an attack okay and this other
guy keeps repeating if everything's
empty
then it doesn't matter okay if
everything's empty people say my life
feels empty you know or Everything feels
empty my family everything I feel empty
and then it means meaningless right it
means things feel empty to me and then
people here in the gaja say everything's
empty and and in normal English it means
nothing feels meaningful to me my life
feels empty you know uh it seems
depressing when the one of the greatest
Buddhists of all time says hey your life
is empty you're
right and then everybody's like oh so my
life has no hope my L my life has no
Beauty my life has no love and he says
that's not what I mean when I say empty
I don't care what you mean when you say
empty that's not what I mean when I say
empty empty to me just means empty to me
just means it doesn't
not come from your seats it doesn't not
come from your seats when you talk about
emptiness you always have to talk in
double negative double negative it's not
something what's it not it's not not
coming from my seats okay it's not not
coming from my seats it's a little bit
difficult word not not coming from my
seats but in the end the meaning is very
very clear uh what's dependent
origination then
everything's coming from your seats
everything's coming from your
seats there's a famous uh expression
called The Marriage of emptiness and
dependent origination they also got
married I did part of the
ceremony I'm just kidding the two
m
m uh
to
in his verses he he did the same thing
okay uh what's it mean uh he
married they had a big wedding what was
the wedding depend origination and
emptiness they had a wedding together
they got married okay they are
together do how do you use that in your
real life how do you use that in your
real life how do you use it with some
someone who's irritating you we already
talked about it okay what's the
dependent
origination they're coming because you
see someone irritating you because you
were irritating last week okay you
started it all right if you're gonna
blame somebody blame yourself okay on
one side what's the
emptiness you never met an irritating
person who wasn't coming from you okay
and you can go over that again and
again we meet irritating PE I have a
prediction when you have a good class
about emptiness when you talk about
emptiness deeply for six seven days okay
the first thing you're GNA do is meet an
irritating person in the airport okay
and you're going to forget the whole
goddamn Club you know I can't believe
they push in front of me in the airport
you know where this stupid person come
from you know
and why we have to build new buildings
here all the time we have to keep all
the emptiness which people left
here it's just like luggage you you know
how many suitcases we got here and
people always leave their extra suitcase
can you just keep it for six months I'll
be back later
and they don't come then they always
leave their emptiness here also we got
all these why we have to keep building
new buildings to keep all the emptiness
which people forgot to take to the
airport with them
okay they left it at Diamond Mountain
they get to the airport the I predict
okay it's the blessing of the DI that
the first thing that happens to you when
you get to the airport you meet an
okay
and this they're going to push in front
of you in the in the line in the airport
you
like where is such a stupid person come
from you know and if you get the
blessing of the Buddha there will be a
little voice in your head from
you okay everybody's saying I want the
blessing of the Buddha that's the
blessing of the Buddha okay those
whisper in your ear is the is the
blessing of the Buddha last thing
uh those blessings are around you all
day those blessings are around you all
day every time someone says something to
you there's a hidden blessing in there
and everybody's like Gua can you teach
us Diamond way Gua can you teach us
Diamond way I'll teach you some Diamond
way
okay everything people say to you in the
airport everything people say to you in
the airplane it's all a message from the
boo okay but you have to re you have to
recognize it okay if you feel like that
you know people say good stuff to you
people say bad stuff to you people don't
even want to talk to you everything's a
message from the Buddha that's Diamond
way that's Diamond way everybody wants
Bells I don't know why ding ding ding
ding ding they gu are you going to wear
this special hat
no that's not Tantra that's not Tantra
is on the airplane when you're going
home Tantra is in the airport okay
Tantra is in this cheap little stores
with the dirty bathrooms on the way to
Tucson
okay right you've been there
right yeah I mean there's
messages everywhere okay and that's
that's Tundra and and take them take the
messages they could be good messages
they could be negative messages but
they're all messages there's this
uh we you want to know
Tantra
uh here's a the first time I taught a
group Tantra at di Mountain they had a
homework and I said they said what is it
I said you go to Tucson tomorrow we
spend two or three days we rented a
motel and I said we're going to go to
the shopping mall
and
uh you're going to look for vaji yini in
the shopping mall so that was their
homework you know I said you got to look
for a Buddha you have to find a Buddha
in the shopping mall so they they were
like okay I can do it you know and uh
one of the students her name is Mercedes
uh she uh she went to uh like the
department store and she was uh in in
the ladies fashion uh Department you
know and the lady said something to her
like you should buy this red dress which
is what bini like that's her
color and and the the lady said uh you
should buy a red
dress and so she thought oh this is
Buddha and she prostrated three
times in the department store
to the sales
lady she called the
police just a crazy woman it's a crazy
woman came to the department store and
it was so much fun okay so uh
okay I say she did the right thing you
know I say you shouldn't hesitate at
those moments okay don't hesitate go for
it you know so you spend a little time
in
the you can ask medicine put
help all right Timothy where are
[Music]
you